A Guide to the Papers of the Dillard Family, 1717-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Oversize Materials
  - Photograph - "Southern University Race Commission at the White House, December 15, 1914,"
  - Photograph of Beta Theta Phi at University of Virginia, 1919.
  - Handwritten book of Mary C. Harmanson - "Vocal Music," 1878 November 29.
  - Color print of Lady Godiva
  - Pictures of unidentified [New Orleans?] church with full choir and organist
  - (L) Daguerreotype, unid. elederly man with glasses [Dillard family] (35), #9498.
  - (M) Daguerreotype, unid. man [Dillard family] (36), #9498.
  - (N) Daguerreotype, "Uncle Jim's little daughter Blanche [Lippincott] (37), #9498.
  - (O) Daguerreotype, unid. young woman, seated [Dillard family] (38), #9498.
  - (L) Daguerreotype, unid. young woman, seated [Dillard family] (39), #9498.
  - (Q) Daguerreotype, unid. young woman [Dillard family] (40), #9498.
  - (R) Daguerreotype, unid. young man [Dillard family] (41), #9498.
  - (S) Daguerreotype, James Lippincott (42), #9498.
  - (T) Ambrotype, "Aunt Carrie" [Mrs. James Lippincott] (43), #9498.
  - (U) Ambrotype, "Aunt Carrie" [Mrs. James Lippincott] (44), #9498.
  - (V) Ambrotype, unid. young woman [Dillard family (45), #9498.
  - (W) Ambrotype, unid. young woman [Dillard family (46), #9498.
  - (X) Ambrotype, unid. young woman with gold jewelry (47), #9498.
  - (A) Tintype, Andrew Eckard Budd (48), #9498.
  - (B) Ambrotype, Andrew Eckard Budd (49), #9498.
  - (C) Tintype, [Laniar] Howe Warren Payson (50), #9498.
  - (D) Tintype, Asa Payson (51), #9498.
  - (E) Tintype cameo, unid. woman [Dillard family] (52), #9498.
  - (F) Tintype, unid. young man [Dillard family] (53), #9498.
  - James H. Dillard papers, #9498.
    University of Pennsylvania diploma; maps of cities around the world.
  - James H. Dillard papers: diplomas and citations, #9498.
  - James H. Dillard Papers, #9498.
    1. Diplomas and citations, 2. Photographs.